[{"answer": "It'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "It's really cold", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "It's pathetic. . . . hey, is it cold out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Scary cold", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It's really cold", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I don't know. What's your definition of scary cold?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "This week. My father got a deal from a friend of his. It's Gor", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I was just thinking. The four of us can't show up with just one bottle of wine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "We'll get some cake. Can you stop off at the bakery", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh, here we go. Why don't we get them a couch? Bring them a nice sectional", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Why don't you just get some Ring Dings at the liquor store", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "It's a fallacy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Why don't YOU go into the store and I'LL wait in the car", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hey, there's a spot right in front of the liquor store. You se", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You see, ho ho,", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well,, this is a little awkward, isn't it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You know we were here ahead of you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It's robust, bold, very dry. As opposed to a Beaujolais which is richer and fruitier. Here's one. Twelve dollars", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "All right but I am going to have to pay you back latter I don't have my wallet", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I know. They're going in first with the last my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You can't beat a that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "We should have had that my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What are we going to do now. If we can't get the Bobka the whole thing's useless", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Carrot cake? Now why is that a cake? You don't make carrots into a cake. I'm sorry", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend? Too scary. You're in the Forrest, oohh", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Okay. Let's go but something. Then we'll get some change", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Don't go shouting we got a hundred dollar bill. People will be jumping out of windows after us", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I am not buying something just to get change", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "There's 22 dollars here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I'm not getting a Penthouse Forum", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It's a hair", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No, we've already got this. I'll just take it off", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, take it back. Let's get another one", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No, really, let's get another one. It will just take a second", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "A little hair? Do you think that makes it better", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What if it's your hair", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Dinner-Party.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I think I got my friend and Fahrikan down there", "qsentId": 40}]